<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Create Screen classes">
   <intro href="/com.twinsoft.convertigo/help/Screens.html">
      <description>
         A <b>Screen Class</b> allows to identify a page (or screen) of a Web application. Convertigo uses the <b>Screen Class</b> to determine which extraction rules to use for a given page. A <b>Screen Class</b> is identified uniquely or by one or more <b>Criteria</b> based on <b>Xpath</b><br/><br/> expressions

Collect in the web site all of the page type containing data as well as those passed to reach them. These pages have to be « marked » as Screen Class so that Convertigo knows at each moment in which page it is.
<br/><br/>
The bold text in this help file is available in (?).
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="Put the browser" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Put the <b>browser area</b>(in the <b>Connector view</b>) on one of the preceeding pages.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Find a specific element" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Click right on an element in the <b>browser area</b> which looks like a specific element of the page or type of page(example: a name, an iamage,  a button).
<br/><br/>In the <b>DOM Area</b> (containing the HTML code under the form of a tree), an underlined element appears in green
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Define a specific element" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         In the <b>DOM Area</b>, press on the &quot;+&quot; of the green element. In the deployed list find an <b>attribute</b> or a <b>tag</b> characterising the screen type of the actual screen
(exemple : <b>attribute</b> « id »,<b>attribute</b> « name »). Click right on this last and press on « Generate selection Xpath ».<br/><br/> In the zone <b>Xpath Area</b> , an Xpath request appears.  The field <b>XPath&apos;s result Area</b> shows the results of the Xpath request for the actual page.
<br/><br/>
(You can press the icon <b>parent node icon</b> to go back in the hierarchy of the <b>DOM Area</b> to find a better element to characterise the web page)
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Verify the exclusivity of your request" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Verify that the Xpath request of the <b>Xpath area</b> doesn't return results for this screen. <br/><br/>For this, test the Xpath request on all the other web pages that are or will become a Screen class. Confirm that they will not sent anything back (root only in <b>XPath&apos;s result Area</b>). <br/><br/>If this is the case return to the web page web to be defined and go to the next phase. If not find an other Xpath request by clicking right --&gt;« Generate selection Xpath » or by manually modifying the request in the zone <b>Xpath Area</b>.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Execute the creation" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         In the view <b>Projects view</b>, click on <b>Screen class</b> « Default Screen class ». <br/> Then click on the icon <b>new screen class icon</b> . Select  &quot;Screen class&quot;, press next and give a name to your screen class.
<br/>
<br/>
(You can also click on the icon <b>new criteria icon</b> to enrich a screen class already existing with a new criteria. The <b>screen class</b> selected in the tab  <b>Projects view</b>  must be the screen class to be enriched. If there are multiple criteria for a screen class, then all have to be satisfied)
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Conclusion" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Your <b>screen class</b> is created and appears in the tab <b>Projects view</b>. Now you can create other <b>screen classes</b>.
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
