<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Create Extractions rules">
   <intro href="/com.twinsoft.convertigo/help/Screens.html">
      <description>
         Extraction rules are tools to transform HTML code (website language) to XML code. « extraction rules » are presented in all screen classes containing information to be extracted.
<br/><br/>
Words in bold in this example is available in (?).
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="Position the browser" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Position the <b>browser area</b> on a screen containing the to be extracted information.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Verify if the web page corresponds with its screen class" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Verify if the page of the <b>browser area</b> is associated with the wanted screen. To do this press the icon <b>Synchronize icon</b>.<br/><br/> In the tab <b>Project view</b>, a <b>screen class</b> has been automatically selected : it is the screen class detected by Convertigo for the actual web page.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Position the information to be extracted in a green frame" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         For this, click right in the <b>Browser area</b> on one of the elements to be extracted followed by eventually making the frame larger with the help of the icon <b>parent node icon</b> .
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Identify l&apos;information by a Xpath" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Find in the <b>DOM area</b> by clicking right--&gt;« Generate selection Xpath » a XPATH request identifying the green frame.
<br/><br/>
The result can be one or more elements depending on the needs.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Choose a rule d&apos;extraction" dialog="true" skip="false" href="http://doc.convertigo.com/JSPWiki/Wiki.jsp?page=CWICWCExtractionRules">
      <description>
         In function of the type of extraction information multiple rules can be choosen.<br/> <br/> 
Cliquez sur (?) pour en voir la liste.<br/> <br/> 
  The rest of this help file describes two of the most used extraction rules.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="L&apos;exemple de la règle Text" dialog="true" skip="true">
      <description>
         Extraction rule « Text » allows to recuperate <b>Text</b> an HTML marker .<br/><br/> To add this rule to a project, select the <b>screen class</b> wanted in the tab <b>Projet view</b> and press the icon  <b>new Extraction rules icon</b>(The Xpath of the <b>Xpath area</b> mist be valid).
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="L&apos;example of the Record rule" dialog="true" skip="true">
      <description>
         The « Record » rule allows to extract information from a list (multiple elements returned by the Xpath request). 
<br/>
<br/>To add this rule to a project, select the <b>screen class</b> wanted in the tab <b>Project view</b> and press the icon <b>new Extraction rules icon</b>(The Xpath of the <b>Xpath area</b> must be valid).
<br/><br/> 
In the tab <b>Properties view</b> you can see a line &quot;Xpath&quot; containing the request permitting to access the information to be extracted (must return a list). A treatment will be executed for each of the results of this request. 
<br/>&gt;Click on the line « Description» just below followed by the button « … ». <br/>&gt;Click on the blue icon for each elementary information in the element of the list.
<br/>&gt; Give names corresponding to the information in the collumn « name » and in the collumn Xpath enter an Xpath request relative to the first onerez une requête Xpath relative to the first one leading to the wanted information.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Verify the working of your Extraction rules" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         To verify that your extraction rules work well, click on the icon <b>XMLize icon</b> next look at the result in the tab <b> Output Tab</b> of the browser.<br/><br/> Attention the icon <b>XMLize icon</b>  of this tab doesn't give the right result !!!
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
