<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Créer des transactions">
   <intro href="/com.twinsoft.convertigo/help/Screens.html">
      <description>
         A transaction creates an automatic navigation in the website op a project and executes certain instructions. Each time Convertigo detects a screen class with extractions rules, the result of extractions with its classes is added to the exit.
<br/><br/>
The bold text in this help file is available in (?).
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="First project (16)" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         The transacation of the project, go an recuperate the information of the announcements of the first response page of google for a sentence entered with parameters<br/><br/>
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Create a new transaction" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         In the tab <b>Projects view</b>,  right click on the file <b>Transactions</b> of your project and next press on <br/><br/>
 &gt;New
<br/><br/> 
&gt;Transaction<br/><br/>
&gt;Transaction HTML<br/><br/>
&gt;Next<br/><br/>
&gt;Finish<br/><br/>
To add entry variables to your transaction, press on the proporiaty &quot;Variables&quot; (in <b>properties view</b>) of your transaction then on &quot;...&quot;. Finally name your variables the way you think is right. From now on these variables are javascript variables and are accessible anywhere in the transaction.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="First project (17)" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         &gt;Create a transaction which you will name &quot;getData&quot;.
<br/><br/>
&gt;Create a variable which you will name &quot;wordToAnalyse&quot;. Also put an entry chain in the field &quot;Default value&quot; This will be the sentence that google will treat.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Create a Handler" dialog="true" skip="false" href="/com.twinsoft.convertigo/help/AlgoHandlers.html">
      <description>
         During the execution of a transaction, Convertigo will execute succesively the instructions contained in the <b>handlers</b> based on the schema of the algorithm of the handlers (available in  (?)).
<br/>
<br/>
To create a <b>handler</b>, click right on the transaction in the tab <b>Projects view</b>, press on &quot;new&quot; next on &quot;Handler&quot;. <br/>Finally select the one(s) you like.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="First project (18)" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         &gt;Right click on the transaction &quot;getData&quot; of the view <b>Projects view</b><br/><br/>
 &gt;Press on &quot;new&quot;next on &quot;Handler&quot;.
 <br/><br/>
 &gt;Click option &quot;Screenclass transaction handler&quot;, choose the class &quot;WelcomePage&quot; then validate.(Leave the option &quot;Entry handler coché&quot; )
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Create a statement" dialog="true" skip="false" href="http://doc.convertigo.com/JSPWiki/Wiki.jsp?page=CWICWCStatements">
      <description>
         For each, there are several instructions (<b>Statement</b>) that can be executed. The list is in (?) .
<br/><br/>
 To add <b>Statement</b> to a <b>handler</b>,  create an Xpath request which sends back the element or the action to be made.<br/>
 Select the <b>handler</b> desired in the tab <b> Projects view</b> and press on the icon <b>new Statement icon</b>.<br/> Choose the adapted Statement.<br/><br/> (You can also create a Statement by clicking right on the <b>handler</b> --&gt; new --&gt; Statement)
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="First project (19)" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         The statement which you are going to create will fill automatically the search zone.<br/><br/>
&gt;Click right in the search zone of google (in the <b>browser area</b>). <br/><br/>
&gt;Then click right followed by &quot;Generate selection Xpath&quot; on the attribute title=&quot;Google Search&quot;. <br/><br/>
&gt;Click on the Handler &quot;onWelcomePageEntry&quot; of the file &quot;Functions&quot; of the transaction  &quot;getData&quot;(Onglet <b>Projects View</b>)<br/><br/>
&gt;Click on the icon <b>New statement icon</b> and select the statement &quot;Input HTML set value&quot;
<br/><br/>
&gt;In the propriaty &quot;Expression&quot; of this statement, replace &quot;//todo&quot; by &quot;wordToAnalyse&quot; (javascript variable created in step 17)
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="First project (20)" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Another statement will have as a goal to press automatically on the button search:
 <br/><br/>
&gt;Right click on the search button (of the <b>browser area</b>). <br/><br/>
&gt;Then click right followed by &quot;Generate selection Xpath&quot; on the attribute value=&quot;Google Search&quot;&quot;. <br/><br/>
&gt;Click on the Handler &quot;onWelcomePageEntry&quot; of the file &quot;Functions&quot; of the transaction  &quot;getData&quot;(Tab <b>Projects View</b>)<br/><br/>
&gt;Finally click on the icon <b>New statement icon</b> and select the statement &quot;Mouse action&quot;
<br/><br/>
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Make your transactions communicative" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         In the tab <b>Projects view</b> click on <b>transaction</b>.<br/> In the tab <b>properties view</b>, put the propriaty « public  Method » to the value true.<br/> Right click on the <b>transaction</b> and click on « Extract WSDL Type » then on « yes ».<br/>  Now the key « Ctrl » and select in the list all the used elements of your transaction (choose them if you do not know which ones are used).
<br/><br/>
Repeat this for all your transactions.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="First project (21)" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         &gt;Click on the transaction &quot;getData&quot;, place the propriaty « public  Method » to the valeu true.
<br/><br/>
&gt;Right click on the transaction &quot;getData&quot;,press on &quot;Extract WSDL type&quot;, click on &quot;oui&quot; then select all the elements of the list (selection multiple avec Ctrl)
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Test your transactions" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         To test a transaction, right click on the selected <b>transaction</b>  and press on  &quot;Execute&quot;. <br/><br/>The result isin the tab <b>Output Tag</b> of the <b>browser area</b>
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
