<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Create Screen classes">
   <intro href="/com.twinsoft.convertigo/help/Screens.html">
      <description>
         A <b>Screen Class</b> allows to identify a page (or screen) of a web application. Convertigo uses the <b>Screen Classes</b> to determine which extraction rules to be used for a given page. A <b>Screen Class</b> is uniquely identified by one or more <b>Criteria</b> based on <b>Xpath</b> expressions.
<br/><br/>
Locate in the web site all the types of pages containing data as well as those used to get there. These pages have to be « marked » as Screen Class for Convertigo to know at each moment in which page it is.
<br/><br/>
The bold text in this help file is available in (?).
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="First project (2)" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         The example project has as goal to:
<br/><br/>
 *Locate the number of results returned by a given google search. <br/><br/>
 *Make a repeating table of the results of the first page
 <br/> <br/>
You will need the welcome page of google: &quot;http://www.google.com/intl/en/&quot;<br/>
And a results page ex:
 &quot;http://www.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=convertigo&quot;
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Put the browser" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Put the <b>browser area</b>(in the <b>Connector view</b>) on one of the pages located previously.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="First project (3)" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         &gt;Put the browser on the first of your pages: http://www.google.com/intl/en/
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Find a specific element" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Right click on an element of the <b>browser area</b> which looks like a specific element of the page or type of page(example: a name, an image, a button).
<br/><br/>In the <b>DOM Area</b> (containing the HTML code in the form of a tree structure), an element will become underlined in green
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="First project (4)" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         &gt;Right click on the button &quot;I&apos;m Feeling Lucky&quot; as the button is only presented in the welcome page.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Define the specific element" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         In the <b>DOM Area</b>, press on the &quot;+&quot; of the element in green. In the deployed list find an <b>attribut</b> or a <b>tag</b> characterising the type of actual screen
(exemple : <b>attribute</b> « id »,<b>attribute</b> « name »). Right click on the last one and press on « Generate selection Xpath ».<br/><br/> In the <b>Xpath Area</b> zone , an Xpath request appears. The space <b>XPath&apos;s result Area</b> shows the results of the Xpath request for the actual page.
<br/><br/>
(You can press on the icon <b>parent node icon</b> to go back in the hierarchy of the <b>DOM Area</b> to find a better element to characterise the web page)
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="First project (5)" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         &gt;Click on the button &quot;+&quot; du &quot;INPUT&quot; underligned<br/><br/>
&gt;Then click on &quot;+&quot; de &quot;attributes&quot;<br/><br/>
&gt;Right click on &quot;name=&quot;btnI&quot;&quot;<br/><br/>
&gt;Finally press on &quot;Generate selection Xpath&quot;
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Verify the exclusivity of your request" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Verify that the Xpath request of the <b>Xpath area</b> does not return results only for this screen. <br/><br/>For this, test the Xpath request on all the other web pages that are or will become Screen classes. Confirm that they do not sent anything back (root only in <b>XPath&apos;s result Area</b>). <br/><br/>If it is the case return on the web page to be defined and go to the next step. If not find an other Xpath request by clicking right --&gt;« Generate selection Xpath » or by a manual modification of the request in the zone <b>Xpath Area</b>.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="First project (6)" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         If you wish, you can test the request in the page http://www.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=convertigo.<br/><br/>
To do this put the browser in the right page, and click in the <b>Xpath Area</b> so that the cursor blinks in the zone and press on the button &quot;enter&quot;  to validate(or on the green arrows &quot;up&quot; then on the green arrow &quot;right&quot;)
<br/><br/>
The result is root seul, your criteria is specified in the welcome page in other words the screen class.
<br/><br/>
 ATTENTION: Return to the page &quot;http://www.google.com/intl/en/&quot; as this is the one we are treating right now!
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Execute the creation" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         In the view <b>Projects view</b>, click on <b>Screen class</b> « Default Screen class ». <br/> Then click on the icon <b>new screen class icon</b> . Select  &quot;Screen class&quot;, press next and then give a name of the caller to your screen class.
<br/>
<br/>
(You can also click on the icon <b>new criteria icon</b> to enrich an already existing screen class. The selected <b>screen class</b> in the tab  <b>Projects view</b> must be the screen class to be enriched. If there are more criteria to a screen class, all have to be satisfied)
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="First project (7)" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         &gt;After having clicked on the entry in the <b>Xpath Area</b> to validate the XPath request, click on the <b>Screen class</b> « Default Screen class » then on the icon <b>new Screen class icon</b>. <br/><br/>&gt;Call your Screen class &quot;WelcomePage&quot;
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Conclusion" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Your <b>screen class</b> has been created and appears in the tab <b>Projects view</b>. You can now create other <b>screen classes</b>.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="First project (8)" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Now realise your second screen class in such a way that all web screens with google results are associated <br/><br/>
&gt;Put yourself on the page: http://www.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=convertigo<br/><br/>
&gt;Click right on the blue line under the search bar indicating the number of results. This bar will be presented with whatever search being done and only in the results pages.<br/><br/>
&gt;Click once on the icon <b>parent node icon</b>(as it has an interesting attribute) and right click followed by a &quot;Generate selection Xpath&quot;on the attribute id=&quot;ssb&quot;<br/><br/>
&gt;Finally click on the <b>Screen class</b> « Default Screen class » and on the icon <b>new screen class icon</b> to create the screen class. Name it &quot;dataPages&quot;
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
